iclipart.com 2015-12-17

# iCLIPART - Downloadable royalty-free clipart images, photos, web graphics, animations, sounds and fonts by subscription.

**PRIVACY POLICY** Overview

At iCLIPART.com, we have adopted the following policy to advise you of your choices regarding the use of your personal information online. This policy describes what types of information we gather about you, how we use it, and your rights to update or correct it. Personal information collected from this site may be stored or processed in Canada or any other country in which iCLIPART.com, or their affiliates, subsidiaries, or agents maintain facilities. By using this site, you consent to any such transfer of information. 

Scope of Policy

This Policy applies to the iCLIPART.com site. This Policy does not apply to other web sites to which we link. You should carefully review the privacy policies of those web sites in order to determine how they treat your personal information.

INFORMATION ABOUT YOU

Information Gathered From All Visitors

Aggregate Data

We gather certain generic information with respect to customers' use of our web site, such as the number of unique visitors, the frequency with which they visit, and the areas on the web site that they favor. These statistics are very much like television ratings that tell the networks how many people tuned in to a program. We only use this type of data in aggregate-that is, we look at the data on a collective basis, in summary form, rather than on an individual basis. This data helps us determine the extent to which our customers use certain parts of our web site, which, in turn, enables us to make it as appealing as possible. We may also provide statistical "ratings" about how our customers collectively use our web site to advertisers, sponsors, and other companies with which we do business ("Business Partners"). We do this so they, too, can understand how often people use their areas of the site in order for them to provide you with the best possible experience. These statistical ratings do not contain any personally identifiable information about you or any of our users.

Cookies

We use a technology called "cookies" on our web site. Cookies are pieces of information or data sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies to make your visit to our web site easier. For example, cookies allow us to recognize you when you re-enter our web site so that you will not have to sign-in each time you visit. Cookies also allow us to count the number of unique and return visitors who use our site. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. If you prefer, you can reset your browser to notify you when you've received a cookie or, alternatively, to refuse to accept cookies. It is important to note that you may not be able to use certain features on our web site if you choose not to accept cookies.

Third Party Advertiser Cookies

We use third-party advertising companies to serve our ads on the Internet. These third-party advertising companies employ cookie and Clear Gif technology (aka 1x1 Pixel .gifs, web bugs) to measure and improve the effectiveness of ads for their clients. To do so, these companies may use anonymous information about your visits to our web site and other web sites. This information can include: date/time of banner ad shown, the banner ad that was shown, their cookie, the IP address. This anonymous information can also be used for online preference marketing purposes. iCLIPART.com does not use or have access to this information.

Advertising Research Cookies

From time-to-time, outside third party research companies may set cookies on your browser regarding exposure to certain ad placements. These cookies may be used later for research purposes if you later opt-in to take a survey. If you choose to take the survey, these companies may examine your browser to see if one of their cookies has been set. If the company detects the cookie in your browser, it will gather only 2 pieces of information from it: where you have seen a particular ad and how many times you have seen it. If you do not want these kinds of cookies to be set to your browser, you can opt-out by clicking here.

IP Addresses

We collect and analyze traffic on our web site by keeping track of the IP addresses of our visitors. IP addresses are unique numeric identifiers that are assigned to each computer browser accessing the Internet. An IP address, by itself, cannot identify you personally. However, when combined with other information provided by your Internet Service Provider (ISP), your IP address can be used to identify the computer originating a message.

Personalizing Your Experience on the Web Site

We try to personalize your experience on our web sites by tracking content you have sent in order to shape our recommendations about the content. We also examine customer traffic patterns and web site usage to help us enhance the design and layout of the site and make it easier to navigate. From time to time, we may send you surveys or solicit your feedback. We use surveys to gauge user interest in new products and premiums we may offer. We will ask for your feedback on site features. We may also use the information to alert you to offers and products in which you have expressed an interest.

Communications from iCLIPART.com

On the iCLIPART.com site, you will be able to sign up for our exclusive iCLIPART.com Newsletter, which alerts you to new features, content, services, and premiums available on our site. The Newsletter may from time to time contain invitations to enhance your iCLIPART.com membership, offers for new products and services from iCLIPART.com, special "Member's Only" premiums, or special offers from our affiliates and our sponsors. These communications are sent to you directly by iCLIPART.com. We do not share your personally identifiable information with any third parties in connection with the Newsletter.

Communications from Our Business Partners

iCLIPART.com also offers you the opportunity to receive money-saving offers, discounts, and promotions from our Business Partners. These communications may come from iCLIPART.com or directly from the Partners themselves. We may also share with them certain demographic, geographic, preference, and other personally identifiable information we have gathered about you. This will help them in directing to you offers that are more likely to be of interest. This program is conducted strictly on an opt-in basis. In order to receive the offers, you must affirmatively check the clearly marked box on our signup pages and registration pages on our site. If you leave the box unchecked, you will not receive any offers. If you do not sign up for the program but later change your mind, you are free at any time to opt-in.

Mandatory Communications

iCLIPART.com reserves the right to communicate with you from time to time about important administrative, policy, legal, credit card, and billing matters, which will affect your use of our web site, including without limitation any alleged violations of our Terms of Service. These communications are mandatory. You cannot opt-out of them.

Information Gathered From Members

If you elect to purchase a Membership on iCLIPART.com, you will be required to provide us with certain personal information, including your name, e-mail address, credit card number, expiration date, and billing address (this required information is subject to change from time to time). There will also be opportunities for you to provide us with additional information regarding your preferences and interests. This information, however, is not required and is completely optional on your part.

iCLIPART.com may also communicate with its members by mail or phone about matters relating to their renewal status, credit card information, related products or services, or any other issues relating to their iCLIPART.com membership. These communications will come directly from iCLIPART.com.

Order Fulfillment

From time to time, you may be given the opportunity to order products and services directly on the iCLIPART.com site, the Newsletters, or in other communications you may receive from iCLIPART.com. These orders are typically fulfilled by iCLIPART.com's business partners directly. To process your order, iCLIPART.com may provide these partners with your name, street address, e-mail address, phone number, and credit card information. iCLIPART.com will limit the types of information shared to the minimum necessary to efficiently process your order. However, in accepting these offers, you become a customer of the business partner and therefore subject to its privacy policy. iCLIPART.com will alert users whenever a Business Partner will be fulfilling an order for products or services ordered on our site. We encourage you to review these companies' privacy policies and only do business with those who adhere to personal information practices with which you are comfortable.

Privacy of Information

We treat all of our content and communications regarding content as private correspondence between the sender and the recipient and will not disclose the contents of any content or communication of that content other than to the intended recipient, except under the specific situations outlined in Disclosure Exceptions, below.

Disclosure Exceptions

Notwithstanding the above policies, we reserve the right to disclose your personal information to appropriate third-parties if we are required to do so by law or we believe that such action is necessary:

* To comply with legal process such as a search warrant, subpoena or court order;  
* To protect the company's rights and property;  
* To investigate reports of users sending material using a false e-mail address or users sending harassing, threatening, or abusive messages;  
* To protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our web site and/or the iCLIPART.com service;  
* To investigate reports of violations of our Terms of Use;  
* To investigate reports of credit card fraud or unauthorized use; or  
* During emergencies, such as when we believe someone's physical safety is at risk.

Your IP address can be accessed within the header of the notification e-mail. Under certain circumstances, recipients, their legal representatives, and/or law enforcement authorities may be able to combine this with information disclosed by ISPs to determine the source of a particular communication. By using this service, you knowingly and voluntarily assume any risks associated with such disclosure.

YOUR CONTROL OVER YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

Opt-In/Changing Your Status

At any time, you can change choices you have previously made as to the use of your personal information. Every communication iCLIPART.com sends you will contain a clearly worded "Opt-In" or "Subscribe" link allowing you to grant your permission for future mailings. This system is automated and must be contacted from the email address you wish to have included. Permission changes will be honored as soon as possible after receipt. Please allow five to seven days for processing.

Editing Your Profile

If you are a registered member, you have the ability to review and correct your personally identifiable information at any time. Simply click on the "My Profile" link at the top of the each page. There, you can change your address information, e-mail type, sign-in, and e-mail permissions.

Data Security

When you place orders for purchased products or access your payment information, we use an advanced encryption technology known as Secure Socket Layer (SSL) to protect the storage and transfer of your data from unauthorized parties. While on a secure page, such as our registration form, a lock or key icon appears on the bottom of your web browser.

In addition to our online security efforts, we take steps to protect your personal data offline, as well.

All of your information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Employees are granted access on a need-to-know basis (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative). Furthermore, ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Finally, the servers on which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment, behind a locked cage.

If you have any questions about the security at our website, you can send an email to [security@iclipart.com](mailto:security@iclipart.com)

Changes to the Privacy Policy

iCLIPART.com will occasionally update this Privacy Policy in response to changing business circumstances and legal developments. When iCLIPART.com posts changes to this Policy, you will see the word "updated" next to the Privacy Policy link on the front page of iCLIPART.com Sites. If there are material changes to this Policy or in how iCLIPART.com uses your personally identifiable information, iCLIPART.com will prominently post such changes prior to implementing the change. iCLIPART.com encourages you to periodically review this Policy to be informed of how we are protecting your information.
